newcave.com 2012-11-28

# New Cave - Free Online Games - Play Without Delay!

.. **Privacy Policy**

We are committed to protecting your privacy online. To further this commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store, and use the information collected about you online.  
This Privacy Policy applies to the NewCave.com website located at www.newcave.com.

About Our Website  
Our Website offer a diverse, current, and exciting mix of online games created by NewCave.com, as well as games created by independent developers and our partners. Players can access our Websites to play games without registering.

What information does we collect?  
We may request and/or collect information from you on a voluntary basis when you: register with us, or when you send questions or comments via e-mail to customer support. The requested information may include personal information such as your name and e-mail address. If you are under the age of 13, you will need your parent or guardian's consent before you can provide any personal information to us for purposes of registration and other online activities.  
This Site uses passive tracking technologies to log non-identifiable information such as IP address, browser type and Site usage (for example: what pages are accessed, how often, referring/exit pages and URLs).

Linking to third party sites  
To provide relevant information not found on our Web site, we may provide links from our Web sites to third party web sites and we encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information. All the downloads and Exe files provided on this site are from a 3rd party and NewCave.com is not responsible for any files or adware that gets installed by their games and screensavers. They contain several adware products so download and install @ your own risk. NewCave.com resumes NO responsibility. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of the content of third party sites'. We hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site.

If you are receiving NewCave.com email advertisements and no longer wish to receive those email messages, you may opt out at the time you receive the message by following the instructions in that email.

If you do not agree with the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy, it may be best to limit your level of interaction with our Site, which could include simply not providing us with personal information. While this will limit the services that our Site is able to provide (chat, friends lists, challenges, etc.), most of the games will remain playable. This option may be best for those who do not wish to provide the mandatory information required to set up an account.

For questions or concerns regarding the use of personal information you submit to us, please contact us at **contact@newcave.com**.
